Some jobs really go for the throat.
Day Shift is a action, fantasy, horror film directed by J.J. Perry.
An LA vampire hunter has a week to come up with the cash
to pay for his kid's tuition and braces.
Trying to make a living these days just might kill him.
Bud Jablonski, played by Jamie Foxx.
Seth, played by Dave Franco.
Heather, played by Natasha Liu Bordizzo.
Jocelyn Jablonski, played by Meagan Good.
Paige Jablonski, played by Zion Broadnax.
Big John Elliott, played by Snoop Dogg.
Day Shift is a 2022 American vampire action comedy film directed by J.
Perry in his directorial debut, written by Tyler Tice and Shay Hatten from a story by Tice, and starring Jamie
Foxx as a blue-collar father whose pool-cleaning job is a front for his work as a vampire hunter.
The film also stars Dave Franco, Snoop Dogg, Natasha Liu Bordizzo, Meagan
Good, Karla Souza, Steve Howey, Scott Adkins and Zion Broadnax.
Netflix released Day Shift on its streaming service on August 12, 2022.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of california, vampire, vampire hunter
(slayer), los angeles, california, buddy comedy.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.